A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of Experimental Medicine, Bound Journals, Series 4 FA1123
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of Experimental Medicine, Bound Journals, Series 4
1969, 1971-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller University Press
FA1123
26.6 Cubic Feet 70 document boxes
Arrangement
Arranged numerically by Volume Number and further arranged chronologically.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for scholarly research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Contains print published versions of the Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1969, 1971-2009.
The series is not fully comprehensive, as Volumes 131, 132, and 137 are not in the archive.
- Bound Journals, 1969, 1971-2009; 4
  - JEM, Volume 130, 1969 July-September (Box 1)
  - JEM, Volume 133, 1971 January-March (Box 1)
  - JEM, Volume 133, 1971 April-June (Box 2)
  - JEM, Volume 134, 1971 July-September (Box 2)
  - JEM, Volume 134, 1971 October-December (Box 3)
  - JEM, Volume 135, 1972 January-March (Box 3)
  - JEM, Volume 135, 1972 April-June (Box 4)
  - JEM, Volume 136, 1972 July-September (Box 4)
  - JEM, Volume 136, 1972 October-December (Box 5)
  - JEM, Volume 138, 1973 July-September (Box 5)
  - JEM, Volume 138, 1973 October-December (Box 6)
  - JEM, Volume 139, 1974 January-March (Box 6)
  - JEM, Volume 139, 1974 April-June (Box 7)
  - JEM, Volume 140, 1974 October-December (Box 7)
  - JEM, Volume 141, 1975 April-June (Box 8)
  - JEM, Volume 142, 1975 July-September (Box 8)
  - JEM, Volume 142, 1975 October-December (Box 9)
  - JEM, Volume 143, 1976 January-March (Box 9)
  - JEM, Volume 143, 1976 April-June (Box 10)
  - JEM, Volume 144, 1976 July-September (Box 10)
  - JEM, Volume 144, 1976 October-December (Box 11)
  - JEM, Volume 145, 1977 January-March (Box 11)
  - JEM, Volume 145, 1977 April-June (Box 12)
  - JEM, Volume 146, 1977 July-September (Box 12)
  - JEM, Volume 146, 1977 October-December (Box 13)
  - JEM, Volume 147, 1978 January-March (Box 13)
  - JEM, Volume 147, 1978 April-June (Box 14)
  - JEM, Volume 148, 1978 July-September (Box 14)
  - JEM, Volume 148, 1978 October-December (Box 15)
  - JEM, Volume 150, 1979 July-September (Box 15)
  - JEM, Volume 150, 1979 October-December (Box 16)
  - JEM, Volume 151, 1980 January-March (Box 16)
  - JEM, Volume 151, 1980 April-June (Box 17)
  - JEM, Volume 152, 1980 July-September (Box 17)
  - JEM, Volume 152, 1980 October-December (Box 18)
  - JEM, Volume 153, 1981 January-March (Box 18)
  - JEM, Volume 153, 1981 April-June (Box 19)
  - JEM, Volume 154, 1981 July-September (Box 19)
  - JEM, Volume 154, 1981 October-December (Box 20)
  - JEM, Volume 155, 1982 January-March (Box 20)
  - JEM, Volume 155, 1982 April-June (Box 21)
  - JEM, Volume 156, 1982 July-September (Box 21)
  - JEM, Volume 156, 1982 October-December (Box 22)
  - JEM, Volume 157, 1983 January-March (Box 22)
  - JEM, Volume 157, 1983 April-June (Box 23)
  - JEM, Volume 158, 1983 July-September (Box 23)
  - JEM, Volume 158, 1983 October-December (Box 24)
  - JEM, Volume 159, 1984 January-March (Box 24)
  - JEM, Volume 159, 1984 April-June (Box 25)
  - JEM, Volume 160, 1984 July-September (Box 25)
  - JEM, Volume 160, 1984 October-December (Box 26)
  - JEM, Volume 161, 1985 January-March (Box 26)
  - JEM, Volume 161, 1985 April-June (Box 27)
  - JEM, Volume 162, 1985 July-September (Box 27)
  - JEM, Volume 162, 1985 October-December (Box 28)
  - JEM, Volume 163, 1986 January-March (Box 28)
  - JEM, Volume 163, 1986 April-June (Box 29)
  - JEM, Volume 164, 1986 July-September (Box 29)
  - JEM, Volume 164, 1986 October-December (Box 30)
  - JEM, Volume 165, 1987 January-March (Box 30)
  - JEM, Volume 165, 1987 April-June (Box 31)
  - JEM, Volume 166, 1987 July-September (Box 31)
  - JEM, Volume 166, 1987 October-December (Box 32)
  - JEM, Volume 167, 1988 January-March (Box 32)
  - JEM, Volume 167, 1988 April-June (Box 33)
  - JEM, Volume 168, 1988 July-September (Box 33)
  - JEM, Volume 168, 1988 October-December (Box 34)
  - JEM, Volume 169, 1989 January-March (Box 34)
  - JEM, Volume 169, 1989 April-June (Box 35)
  - JEM, Volume 170, 1989 July-September (Box 35)
  - JEM, Volume 170, 1989 October-December (Box 36)
  - JEM, Volume 171, 1990 January-March (Box 36)
  - JEM, Volume 171, 1990 April-June (Box 37)
  - JEM, Volume 172, 1990 July-September (Box 37)
  - JEM, Volume 172, 1990 October-December (Box 38)
  - JEM, Volume 173, 1991 January-June (Box 38)
  - JEM, Volume 174, 1991 July-December (Box 39)
  - JEM, Volume 175, 1992 January-March (Box 39)
  - JEM, Volume 175, 1992 April-June (Box 40)
  - JEM, Volume 176, 1992 October-December (Box 40)
  - JEM, Volume 177, 1993 January-June (Box 41)
  - JEM, Volume 178, 1993 July-December (Box 42)
  - JEM, Volume 179, 1994 January-June (Box 43)
  - JEM, Volume 180, 1994 July-December (Box 44)
  - JEM, Volume 181, 1995 January-June (Box 45)
  - JEM, Volume 182, 1995 July-December (Box 46)
  - JEM, Volume 183, 1996 January-June (Box 47)
  - JEM, Volume 184, 1996 July-December (Box 48)
  - JEM, Volume 185, 1997 January-June (Box 49)
  - JEM, Volume 186, 1997 July-December (Box 50)
  - JEM, Volume 187, 1998 (Box 51)
  - JEM, Volume 188, 1998 (Box 51)
  - JEM, Volume 188, 1998 October-December (Box 52)
  - JEM, Volume 189, 1999 January-March (Box 52)
  - JEM, Volume 189, 1999 April-June (Box 53)
  - JEM, Volume 190, 1999 July-September (Box 53)
  - JEM, Volume 190, 1999 October-December (Box 54)
  - JEM, Volume 191, 2000 January-March (Box 54)
  - JEM, Volume 191, 2000 April-June (Box 55)
  - JEM, Volume 192, 2000 July-September (Box 55)
  - JEM, Volume 192, 2000 October-December (Box 56)
  - JEM, Volume 193, 2001 January-March (Box 56)
  - JEM, Volume 193, 2001 April-June (Box 57)
  - JEM, Volume 194, 2001 July-September (Box 57)
  - JEM, Volume 194, 2001 October-December (Box 58)
  - JEM, Volume 195, 2002 January-March (Box 58)
  - JEM, Volume 195, 2002 April-June (Box 59)
  - JEM, Volume 196, 2002 July-September (Box 59)
  - JEM, Volume 196, 2002 October-December (Box 60)
  - JEM, Volume 197, 2003 January-March (Box 60)
  - JEM, Volume 197, 2003 April-June (Box 61)
  - JEM, Volume 198, 2003 July-September (Box 61)
  - JEM, Volume 198, 2003 October-December (Box 62)
  - JEM, Volume 199, 2004 January-March (Box 62)
  - JEM, Volume 199, 2004 April-June (Box 63)
  - JEM, Volume 200, 2004 July-September (Box 63)
  - JEM, Volume 200, 2004 October-December (Box 64)
  - JEM, Volume 201, 2005 January-March (Box 64)
  - JEM, Volume 201, 2005 April-June (Box 65)
  - JEM, Volume 202, 2005 July-September (Box 65)
  - JEM, Volume 202, 2005 October-December (Box 66)
  - JEM, Volume 203, 2006 January-June (Box 66)
  - JEM, Volume 203, 2006 July-December (Box 67)
  - JEM, Volume 204, 2007 January-April (Box 67)
  - JEM, Volume 204, 2007 May-December (Box 68)
  - JEM, Volume 205, 2008 January-August (Box 69)
  - JEM, Volume 205, 2008 September-December (Box 70)
  - JEM, Volume 206, 2009 January-April (Box 70)